[{"answer": "You certainly may.", "docId": "110209pmt", "aSentId": 25, "question": "Mr. Trump, can I call you Donald finally?", "qSentId": 24}, {"answer": "Well, I know a lot of politicians and I can tell you that they're not so different from this guy other than they don't do it on Facebook or whatever he was doing it on, and there's a lot of affairs going on in Congress.", "docId": "110209pmt", "aSentId": 46, "question": "What is your reaction to that breaking news?", "qSentId": 45}, {"answer": "If I was honest I certainly was.", "docId": "110209pmt", "aSentId": 64, "question": "What's the answer?", "qSentId": 63}, {"answer": "Well, I think the first thing I'd do is announce very strongly that we're going to tax Chinese products, 25 percent tax on all Chinese products.", "docId": "110209pmt", "aSentId": 98, "question": "What are the top priorities for President Trump?", "qSentId": 97}, {"answer": "I see them as the enemy.", "docId": "110209pmt", "aSentId": 111, "question": "ORGAN: You see them as the enemy, don't you, Donald?", "qSentId": 110}, {"answer": "I think they're smart but I don't think they have any savvy.", "docId": "110209pmt", "aSentId": 129, "question": "Do you think we have smart enough people to deal with the Chinese and the Indians and these new competitors out there in business?", "qSentId": 128}, {"answer": "I don't think they're friends.", "docId": "110209pmt", "aSentId": 162, "question": "Can't we work with them?", "qSentId": 161}, {"answer": "You need to have people that know how to deal with the Chinese.", "docId": "110209pmt", "aSentId": 237, "question": "And don't we just need more people like you to compete with them?", "qSentId": 236}, {"answer": "A woman reached out to us.", "docId": "110209pmt", "aSentId": 260, "question": "How did you get this?", "qSentId": 259}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "110209pmt", "aSentId": 273, "question": "Are you taken aback by the speed of his resignation?", "qSentId": 272}, {"answer": "I've never heard of anybody -- well, you feel sorry for the person but this was really ridiculous.", "docId": "110209pmt", "aSentId": 300, "question": "Do you feel sorry for him?", "qSentId": 299}, {"answer": "Well, it's morality but it's also bad judgment.", "docId": "110209pmt", "aSentId": 306, "question": "Is he more a question for you than just a bad judgment rather than the morality of it?", "qSentId": 305}, {"answer": "If he's married and starts sending pictures of himself.", "docId": "110209pmt", "aSentId": 311, "question": "Would you fire a senior employee at your company for a similar thing?", "qSentId": 310}, {"answer": "RUMP: Well, I thought -- I'm a Republican.", "docId": "110209pmt", "aSentId": 334, "question": "Do you still feel that was the wrong way around, that perhaps we get our priorities wrong?", "qSentId": 333}, {"answer": "I think he's a nice man.", "docId": "110209pmt", "aSentId": 368, "question": "What is your -- what is your view of President Obama right now?", "qSentId": 367}, {"answer": "But we'll see what happens.", "docId": "110209pmt", "aSentId": 379, "question": "But is this the problem?", "qSentId": 378}, {"answer": "I don't think there is a leader right now of the candidates.", "docId": "110209pmt", "aSentId": 381, "question": "Who is leading the Republicans and who should be?", "qSentId": 380}, {"answer": "Well, I am tempted to run, but I think the primary reason I'm tempted -- I guess, yes, I think I could win, otherwise I wouldn't do it.", "docId": "110209pmt", "aSentId": 390, "question": "Is this -- is this precisely why you're so tempted to run?", "qSentId": 389}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "110209pmt", "aSentId": 407, "question": "Defensive?", "qSentId": 406}, {"answer": "Well --", "docId": "110209pmt", "aSentId": 450, "question": "If you were president would you take all American troops out of Afghanistan and Iraq now?", "qSentId": 449}, {"answer": "Well, it's interesting, Saudi, as I mentioned to you tonight, the other breaking news is that the king of Saudi Arabia has been very firm with President Obama basically telling him to leave off Mubarak.", "docId": "110209pmt", "aSentId": 469, "question": "OK?", "qSentId": 468}, {"answer": "They're standing up for the first time because they don't respect us anymore.", "docId": "110209pmt", "aSentId": 472, "question": "And so, what do you think of that situation as it's developing where you're beginning to see the old order in the Middle East standing up to America and saying, this is our business not yours?", "qSentId": 471}, {"answer": "Companies like General Motors, companies like Coca-Cola.", "docId": "110209pmt", "aSentId": 493, "question": "They do?", "qSentId": 492}, {"answer": "I think it's great.", "docId": "110209pmt", "aSentId": 499, "question": "Isn't that what you would do instinctively?", "qSentId": 498}, {"answer": "Look, you've always going to have problems with financial systems.", "docId": "110209pmt", "aSentId": 508, "question": "What was wrong with the system here that should now be put right properly?", "qSentId": 507}, {"answer": "Look what happened with Chase today.", "docId": "110209pmt", "aSentId": 516, "question": "Should bankers -- the same bankers that got us into the mess now be allowed, in a regulation way, to be awarding themselves huge bonuses?", "qSentId": 515}, {"answer": "They want me to say Obama.", "docId": "110209pmt", "aSentId": 538, "question": "What do they want you to say?", "qSentId": 537}, {"answer": "Not everybody can think big.", "docId": "110209pmt", "aSentId": 597, "question": "Is that your steely philosophy?", "qSentId": 596}, {"answer": "That's right.", "docId": "110209pmt", "aSentId": 616, "question": "Have you?", "qSentId": 615}, {"answer": "And I don't drink coffee.", "docId": "110209pmt", "aSentId": 625, "question": "You don't even drink coffee, do you?", "qSentId": 624}, {"answer": "I respect women.", "docId": "110209pmt", "aSentId": 631, "question": "Women are your vice, right?", "qSentId": 630}, {"answer": "So far, my kids have been following my lead.", "docId": "110209pmt", "aSentId": 654, "question": "Do they follow your lead?", "qSentId": 653}, {"answer": "He hated the taste.", "docId": "110209pmt", "aSentId": 674, "question": "Even though he hated the taste to start with?", "qSentId": 673}, {"answer": "There's a banker -- and obviously I'm not going to mention names.", "docId": "110209pmt", "aSentId": 685, "question": "What do you think of that?", "qSentId": 684}, {"answer": "He just retired.", "docId": "110209pmt", "aSentId": 705, "question": "Is he still a senior banker?", "qSentId": 704}, {"answer": "RUMP: I lost respect for him.", "docId": "110209pmt", "aSentId": 709, "question": "You lost respect for him?", "qSentId": 708}, {"answer": "Well, I guess it's my looks.", "docId": "110209pmt", "aSentId": 720, "question": "What's the secret?", "qSentId": 719}, {"answer": "Well, business is more important because I'm a happily married man.", "docId": "110209pmt", "aSentId": 733, "question": "What's more important to you, women or business?", "qSentId": 732}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "110209pmt", "aSentId": 742, "question": "With my wife?", "qSentId": 741}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "110209pmt", "aSentId": 747, "question": "Would that include my wife?", "qSentId": 746}, {"answer": "Well, I think I've been a very good husband lately.", "docId": "110209pmt", "aSentId": 760, "question": "What kind of husband have you been, do you think?", "qSentId": 759}, {"answer": "I think I am pretty vain.", "docId": "110209pmt", "aSentId": 780, "question": "Are you vain?", "qSentId": 779}, {"answer": "Well, it's a lot different looks.", "docId": "110209pmt", "aSentId": 785, "question": "What is the look?", "qSentId": 784}, {"answer": "Well, you've got a long way to go.", "docId": "110209pmt", "aSentId": 791, "question": "ORGAN: If I want the look, what is it?", "qSentId": 790}, {"answer": "Well, I guess it is.", "docId": "110209pmt", "aSentId": 810, "question": "So it's all real, but it's probably the most famous hair in America, isn't it?", "qSentId": 809}, {"answer": "I don't think so.", "docId": "110209pmt", "aSentId": 830, "question": "Are they demeaning to women, do you think?", "qSentId": 829}, {"answer": "Pretty tough.", "docId": "110209pmt", "aSentId": 882, "question": "How tough a dad are you, do you think?", "qSentId": 881}, {"answer": "That's a very tough thing.", "docId": "110209pmt", "aSentId": 892, "question": "If one of -- it would have to be Ivanka in your case -- had gone off the rails like Lindsay Lohan has gone off the rails, how would you deal with that?", "qSentId": 891}, {"answer": "I heard she had some very nice things to say.", "docId": "110209pmt", "aSentId": 909, "question": "Are you ready to put it behind you?", "qSentId": 908}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "110209pmt", "aSentId": 917, "question": "Are you ever going to retire?", "qSentId": 916}]